(Amy:)completely rocked
my girlfriend's world in bed.
(stammers)
Amy...
(Amy:)You know the rules.
(Penny:)Drink.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)Yeah, go ahead.
(Leonard:)That's right.
(Sheldon:)All right, my turn.
(Sheldon:)Mm...
(Sheldon:)Oh, I know.
(Penny:)Never have I ever
kept a secret bank account,
(Sheldon:)because I think
my wife can't handle money.
(Sheldon:)Did I win?
(Sheldon:)I feel like I won.
(Penny:)I can't believe this.
(Penny:)You realize I make
more money than you?
(Leonard:)I don't, I know,
but this isn't a big deal.
(Leonard:)It's just a little savings
I put aside.
(Penny:)We're married.
(Penny:)We're supposed
to share everything.
(Leonard:)What... you mean, like,
your massive credit card debt?
(door slams)
(Sheldon:)I'm calling it.
(Sheldon:)I won.